(window["webpackJsonp"]=window["webpackJsonp"]||[]).push([["chunk-7b2b82d5"],{"268e":function(e,a,n){"use strict";n.r(a);var t=function(){var e=this,a=e._self._c;return a("transition",{attrs:{name:"fade"}},[a("el-container",{directives:[{name:"show",rawName:"v-show",value:e.$store.state.isLoaded,expression:"$store.state.isLoaded"}],attrs:{direction:"vertical"}},[a("el-header",{attrs:{height:"60px"}},[a("h1",[e._v("\n        "+e._s(e.$t("Experimental Features"))+"\n      ")])]),e._v(" "),a("el-main",[a("el-row",{attrs:{gutter:20}},[a("el-col",{attrs:{span:15}},[a("div",{staticClass:"setup-form"},[a("el-form",{ref:"form",attrs:{model:e.form,"label-width":"0px"}},[a("el-form-item",[a("InfoBlock",{attrs:{type:"info",title:e.$t("Experimental Features that have not been officially released can be enabled here, configuration is only saved locally in the browser.")}})],1),e._v(" "),a("el-form-item",{attrs:{prop:"PIPTool"}},[a("el-switch",{attrs:{"active-text":e.$t("Enable PIP Tool")},model:{value:e.form.PIPTool,callback:function(a){e.$set(e.form,"PIPTool",a)},expression:"form.PIPTool"}}),e._v(" "),a("div",{staticClass:"text-small form-item-tip"},[e._v("\n                  "+e._s(e.$t("For installing 3rd-party Python package"))+"\n                  "),a("br"),a("i18n",{attrs:{path:"Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} PIP tool"}},[a("i",{staticClass:"fa fa-fw fa-long-arrow-right"})])],1)],1),e._v(" "),a("el-form-item",{attrs:{prop:"FileManage"}},[a("el-switch",{attrs:{"active-text":e.$t("Enable File Manage")},model:{value:e.form.FileManage,callback:function(a){e.$set(e.form,"FileManage",a)},expression:"form.FileManage"}}),e._v(" "),a("div",{staticClass:"text-small form-item-tip"},[e._v("\n                  "+e._s(e.$t("For managing files on the server side"))+"\n                  "),a("br"),a("i18n",{attrs:{path:"Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} File Manage"}},[a("i",{staticClass:"fa fa-fw fa-long-arrow-right"})])],1)],1),e._v(" "),a("el-form-item",{attrs:{prop:"FileService"}},[a("el-switch",{attrs:{"active-text":e.$t("Enable File Service")},model:{value:e.form.FileService,callback:function(a){e.$set(e.form,"FileService",a)},expression:"form.FileService"}}),e._v(" "),a("div",{staticClass:"text-small form-item-tip"},[e._v("\n                  "+e._s(e.$t("For serving resource directories as file services"))+"\n                  "),a("br"),a("i18n",{attrs:{path:"Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} File Service"}},[a("i",{staticClass:"fa fa-fw fa-long-arrow-right"})])],1)],1),e._v(" "),a("el-form-item",{attrs:{prop:"FuncCacheManage"}},[a("el-switch",{attrs:{"active-text":e.$t("Enable Func Cache Manage")},model:{value:e.form.FuncCacheManage,callback:function(a){e.$set(e.form,"FuncCacheManage",a)},expression:"form.FuncCacheManage"}}),e._v(" "),a("div",{staticClass:"text-small form-item-tip"},[e._v("\n                  "+e._s(e.$t("For managing cached data from Scripts"))+"\n                  "),a("br"),a("i18n",{attrs:{path:"Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Func Cache Manage"}},[a("i",{staticClass:"fa fa-fw fa-long-arrow-right"})])],1)],1),e._v(" "),a("el-form-item",{attrs:{prop:"FuncStoreManage"}},[a("el-switch",{attrs:{"active-text":e.$t("Enable Func Store Manage")},model:{value:e.form.FuncStoreManage,callback:function(a){e.$set(e.form,"FuncStoreManage",a)},expression:"form.FuncStoreManage"}}),e._v(" "),a("div",{staticClass:"text-small form-item-tip"},[e._v("\n                  "+e._s(e.$t("For managing stored data from Scripts"))+"\n                  "),a("br"),a("i18n",{attrs:{path:"Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Func Store Manage"}},[a("i",{staticClass:"fa fa-fw fa-long-arrow-right"})])],1)],1),e._v(" "),a("el-form-item",{attrs:{prop:"FuncDoc"}},[a("el-switch",{attrs:{"active-text":e.$t("Enable Func Doc")},model:{value:e.form.FuncDoc,callback:function(a){e.$set(e.form,"FuncDoc",a)},expression:"form.FuncDoc"}}),e._v(" "),a("div",{staticClass:"text-small form-item-tip"},[e._v("\n                  "+e._s(e.$t("Document page for all Python functions with DFF.API decorator"))+"\n                  "),a("br"),a("i18n",{attrs:{path:"Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Func Doc"}},[a("i",{staticClass:"fa fa-fw fa-long-arrow-right"})])],1)],1),e._v(" "),a("el-form-item",{attrs:{prop:"OpenAPIDoc"}},[a("el-switch",{attrs:{"active-text":e.$t("Enable Open API Doc")},model:{value:e.form.OpenAPIDoc,callback:function(a){e.$set(e.form,"OpenAPIDoc",a)},expression:"form.OpenAPIDoc"}}),e._v(" "),a("div",{staticClass:"text-small form-item-tip"},[e._v("\n                  "+e._s(e.$t("Document page for Open API powered by Swagger"))+"\n                  "),a("br"),a("i18n",{attrs:{path:"Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Open API Doc"}},[a("i",{staticClass:"fa fa-fw fa-long-arrow-right"})])],1)],1),e._v(" "),e.$store.getters.isAdmin?a("el-form-item",{attrs:{prop:"AccessKeys"}},[a("el-switch",{attrs:{"active-text":e.$t("Enable Access Key Manage")},model:{value:e.form.AccessKeys,callback:function(a){e.$set(e.form,"AccessKeys",a)},expression:"form.AccessKeys"}}),e._v(" "),a("div",{staticClass:"text-small form-item-tip"},[e._v("\n                  "+e._s(e.$t("For allowing external systems to call the Open APIs of this system"))+"\n                  "),a("br"),a("i18n",{attrs:{path:"Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Access Keys"}},[a("i",{staticClass:"fa fa-fw fa-long-arrow-right"})])],1)],1):e._e()],1)],1)]),e._v(" "),a("el-col",{staticClass:"hidden-md-and-down",attrs:{span:9}})],1)],1)],1)],1)},c=[],s=n("c7eb"),r=n("1da1"),o=(n("b64b"),n("d3b7"),n("159b"),{name:"ExperimentalFeatures",components:{},watch:{$route:{immediate:!0,handler:function(e,a){var n=this;return Object(r["a"])(Object(s["a"])().mark((function e(){return Object(s["a"])().wrap((function(e){while(1)switch(e.prev=e.next){case 0:return e.next=2,n.loadData();case 2:case"end":return e.stop()}}),e)})))()}},form:{deep:!0,handler:function(e,a){var n=this.T.jsonCopy(this.form);this.$store.commit("updateEnabledExperimentalFeatures",n)}}},methods:{loadData:function(){var e=this;return Object(r["a"])(Object(s["a"])().mark((function a(){var n,t;return Object(s["a"])().wrap((function(a){while(1)switch(a.prev=a.next){case 0:n=e.T.jsonCopy(e.$store.state.enabledExperimentalFeatureMap)||{},t={},Object.keys(e.form).forEach((function(e){return t[e]=!!n[e]})),e.form=t,e.$store.commit("updateLoadStatus",!0);case 5:case"end":return a.stop()}}),a)})))()}},computed:{},props:{},data:function(){return{form:{PIPTool:!1,FileManage:!1,FileService:!1,FuncCacheManage:!1,FuncStoreManage:!1,FuncDoc:!1,OpenAPIDoc:!1,AccessKeys:!1}}}}),i=o,l=n("2877"),m=n("77f8"),g=n("d527"),f=n("3077"),p=Object(l["a"])(i,t,c,!1,null,"614f4d50",null);"function"===typeof m["default"]&&Object(m["default"])(p),"function"===typeof g["default"]&&Object(g["default"])(p),"function"===typeof f["default"]&&Object(f["default"])(p);a["default"]=p.exports},3077:function(e,a,n){"use strict";var t=n("b94c"),c=n.n(t);a["default"]=c.a},"64b6":function(e,a){e.exports=function(e){e.options.__i18n=e.options.__i18n||[],e.options.__i18n.push('{"zh-HK":{"Abnormal Request Page for current system":"本系統異常請求查看頁面","Document page for Open API powered by Swagger":"基於 Swagger 的 Open API 文檔","Document page for all Python functions with DFF.API decorator":"函數文檔，包含所有添加 DFF.API 裝飾器的 Python 函數","Enable Abnormal Request Page":"啓用異常請求查看頁面","Enable Access Key Manage":"啓用 Access Key 管理","Enable File Manage":"啓用文件管理","Enable File Service":"啓用文件服務","Enable Func Cache Manage":"啓用函數緩存管理","Enable Func Doc":"啓用函數文檔","Enable Func Store Manage":"啓用函數存儲管理","Enable Open API Doc":"啓用 Open API 文檔","Enable PIP Tool":"啓用 PIP 工具","Enable Script Failure Page":"啓用腳本故障查看頁面","Enable Script Log Page":"啓用腳本日誌查看頁面","Enable System Log Page":"啓用系統日誌查看頁面","Enable System Status Page":"啓用系統狀態查看頁面","Experimental Features that have not been officially released can be enabled here, configuration is only saved locally in the browser.":"一些尚未正式公開的實驗性功能可在本頁面開啓，本頁面配置僅保存在瀏覽器本地","Failure Page for Script runtime":"腳本運行時故障查看頁面","For allowing external systems to call the Open APIs of this system":"用於管理允許外部系統調用本系統的 Open API","For installing 3rd-party Python package":"用於安裝第三方 Python 包","For managing cached data from Scripts":"用於管理腳本產生的緩存數據","For managing files on the server side":"用於管理服務器端文件","For managing stored data from Scripts":"用於管理腳本產生的存儲數據","For serving resource directories as file services":"用於將資源目錄提供為文件服務","Log Page for Script runtime":"腳本運行時日誌查看頁面","Log Page for current system":"本系統日誌查看頁面","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Abnormal Requests":"啓用後，可在「管理」{0}「異常請求」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Access Keys":"啓用後，可在「管理」{0}「Access Keys」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} File Manage":"啓用後，可在「管理」{0}「文件管理」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} File Service":"啓用後，可在「管理」{0}「文件服務」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Func Cache Manage":"啓用後，可在「管理」{0}「函數緩存管理」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Func Doc":"啓用後，可在「管理」{0}「函數文檔」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Func Store Manage":"啓用後，可在「管理」{0}「函數存儲管理」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Open API Doc":"啓用後，可在「管理」{0}「Open API 文檔」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} PIP tool":"啓用後，可在「管理」{0}「PIP 工具」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Script Failures":"啓用後，可在「管理」{0}「腳本故障」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Script Logs":"啓用後，可在「管理」{0}「腳本日誌」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} System Logs":"啓用後，可在「管理」{0}「系統日誌」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} System Status":"啓用後，可在「管理」{0}「系統狀態」進入","Status Page for current system":"本系統狀態查看頁面"}}'),delete e.options._Ctor}},6845:function(e,a){e.exports=function(e){e.options.__i18n=e.options.__i18n||[],e.options.__i18n.push('{"zh-CN":{"Experimental Features that have not been officially released can be enabled here, configuration is only saved locally in the browser.":"一些尚未正式公开的实验性功能可在本页面开启，本页面配置仅保存在浏览器本地","Enable PIP Tool":"启用 PIP 工具","For installing 3rd-party Python package":"用于安装第三方 Python 包","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} PIP tool":"启用后，可在「管理」{0}「PIP 工具」进入","Enable File Manage":"启用文件管理","For managing files on the server side":"用于管理服务器端文件","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} File Manage":"启用后，可在「管理」{0}「文件管理」进入","Enable File Service":"启用文件服务","For serving resource directories as file services":"用于将资源目录提供为文件服务","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} File Service":"启用后，可在「管理」{0}「文件服务」进入","Enable Func Cache Manage":"启用函数缓存管理","For managing cached data from Scripts":"用于管理脚本产生的缓存数据","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Func Cache Manage":"启用后，可在「管理」{0}「函数缓存管理」进入","Enable Func Store Manage":"启用函数存储管理","For managing stored data from Scripts":"用于管理脚本产生的存储数据","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Func Store Manage":"启用后，可在「管理」{0}「函数存储管理」进入","Enable Func Doc":"启用函数文档","Document page for all Python functions with DFF.API decorator":"函数文档，包含所有添加 DFF.API 装饰器的 Python 函数","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Func Doc":"启用后，可在「管理」{0}「函数文档」进入","Enable Open API Doc":"启用 Open API 文档","Document page for Open API powered by Swagger":"基于 Swagger 的 Open API 文档","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Open API Doc":"启用后，可在「管理」{0}「Open API 文档」进入","Enable System Status Page":"启用系统状态查看页面","Status Page for current system":"本系统状态查看页面","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} System Status":"启用后，可在「管理」{0}「系统状态」进入","Enable System Log Page":"启用系统日志查看页面","Log Page for current system":"本系统日志查看页面","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} System Logs":"启用后，可在「管理」{0}「系统日志」进入","Enable Abnormal Request Page":"启用异常请求查看页面","Abnormal Request Page for current system":"本系统异常请求查看页面","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Abnormal Requests":"启用后，可在「管理」{0}「异常请求」进入","Enable Script Log Page":"启用脚本日志查看页面","Log Page for Script runtime":"脚本运行时日志查看页面","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Script Logs":"启用后，可在「管理」{0}「脚本日志」进入","Enable Script Failure Page":"启用脚本故障查看页面","Failure Page for Script runtime":"脚本运行时故障查看页面","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Script Failures":"启用后，可在「管理」{0}「脚本故障」进入","Enable Access Key Manage":"启用 Access Key 管理","For allowing external systems to call the Open APIs of this system":"用于管理允许外部系统调用本系统的 Open API","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Access Keys":"启用后，可在「管理」{0}「Access Keys」进入"}}'),delete e.options._Ctor}},"77f8":function(e,a,n){"use strict";var t=n("6845"),c=n.n(t);a["default"]=c.a},b94c:function(e,a){e.exports=function(e){e.options.__i18n=e.options.__i18n||[],e.options.__i18n.push('{"zh-TW":{"Abnormal Request Page for current system":"本系統異常請求檢視頁面","Document page for Open API powered by Swagger":"基於 Swagger 的 Open API 文件","Document page for all Python functions with DFF.API decorator":"函式文件，包含所有新增 DFF.API 裝飾器的 Python 函式","Enable Abnormal Request Page":"啟用異常請求檢視頁面","Enable Access Key Manage":"啟用 Access Key 管理","Enable File Manage":"啟用檔案管理","Enable File Service":"啟用檔案服務","Enable Func Cache Manage":"啟用函式快取管理","Enable Func Doc":"啟用函式文件","Enable Func Store Manage":"啟用函式儲存管理","Enable Open API Doc":"啟用 Open API 文件","Enable PIP Tool":"啟用 PIP 工具","Enable Script Failure Page":"啟用指令碼故障檢視頁面","Enable Script Log Page":"啟用指令碼日誌檢視頁面","Enable System Log Page":"啟用系統日誌檢視頁面","Enable System Status Page":"啟用系統狀態檢視頁面","Experimental Features that have not been officially released can be enabled here, configuration is only saved locally in the browser.":"一些尚未正式公開的實驗性功能可在本頁面開啟，本頁面配置僅儲存在瀏覽器本地","Failure Page for Script runtime":"指令碼執行時故障檢視頁面","For allowing external systems to call the Open APIs of this system":"用於管理允許外部系統呼叫本系統的 Open API","For installing 3rd-party Python package":"用於安裝第三方 Python 包","For managing cached data from Scripts":"用於管理指令碼產生的快取資料","For managing files on the server side":"用於管理伺服器端檔案","For managing stored data from Scripts":"用於管理指令碼產生的儲存資料","For serving resource directories as file services":"用於將資源目錄提供為檔案服務","Log Page for Script runtime":"指令碼執行時日誌檢視頁面","Log Page for current system":"本系統日誌檢視頁面","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Abnormal Requests":"啟用後，可在「管理」{0}「異常請求」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Access Keys":"啟用後，可在「管理」{0}「Access Keys」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} File Manage":"啟用後，可在「管理」{0}「檔案管理」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} File Service":"啟用後，可在「管理」{0}「檔案服務」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Func Cache Manage":"啟用後，可在「管理」{0}「函式快取管理」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Func Doc":"啟用後，可在「管理」{0}「函式文件」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Func Store Manage":"啟用後，可在「管理」{0}「函式儲存管理」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Open API Doc":"啟用後，可在「管理」{0}「Open API 文件」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} PIP tool":"啟用後，可在「管理」{0}「PIP 工具」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Script Failures":"啟用後，可在「管理」{0}「指令碼故障」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} Script Logs":"啟用後，可在「管理」{0}「指令碼日誌」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} System Logs":"啟用後，可在「管理」{0}「系統日誌」進入","Once enabled, it can be accessed from Management page {0} System Status":"啟用後，可在「管理」{0}「系統狀態」進入","Status Page for current system":"本系統狀態檢視頁面"}}'),delete e.options._Ctor}},d527:function(e,a,n){"use strict";var t=n("64b6"),c=n.n(t);a["default"]=c.a}}]);